Local 1199 Records 5510
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Social activities, 1960-1963 (Box 102, Folder 5)
- Welfare inquiries, 1959-1962 (Box 102, Folder 6)
- Paid bills, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 7)
- Articles on hospital unions and religion, 1960-1962 (Box 102, Folder 8)
- Newspaper clippings [folder 1 of 4] (Box 103, Folder 1)
- Newspaper clippings [folder 2 of 4] (Box 104, Folder 1)
- Newspaper clippings [folder 3 of 4] (Box 105, Folder 1)
- Newspaper clippings [folder 4 of 4] (Box 106, Folder 1)